[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Виходити заміж, одружуватися' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けっこんします"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Реєструвати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とうろくします"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'реєстрація' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とうろく"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Рибалити' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "つりします"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Проводити засідання' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいぎします"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'засідання, конференція' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいぎ"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Їсти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょくじします"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'їжа' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょくじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Робити покупки' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいものします"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'покупки' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいもの"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Я зголоднів “Живіт став пустим”' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おなかがすきました"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Я ситий “Живіт став повним' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おなかがいっぱい"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Хочу пити “Горло пересохло”' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "のどがかわきました"
    }, 
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Так і поступимо (вираження згоди)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "そうしましょう"
    }
]
